So, what's going on, Shinwa?
I don't know anything more than you do.
Where are the choppers?
Gurren said they would be here waiting to evacuate us.
We're not safe here. The vampires will be close behind. We can't just stand around.
Major General, these directives were in the flight control room. I think they're for us.
Well, what does it say?
To stand by and wait for new orders.
Stand by?
This is all your fault, you spoiled little bitch!
Yayoi, Kageyama, they're both dead because you betrayed us and protected that vampire!
It's not fair that you're still alive! Maybe you should join them!
It's all your fault!
You got my friends killed!
I'm sorry.
I'm not forgiving you that easily!
Don't pay for what you did!
Stop! It's fine, you guys!
I don't want your apology!
Save your breath! It won't bring my friends back!
They're bleeding in the streets!
You killed them!
Rika, pull yourself together.
Killing her isn't going to help.
But, Makoto...
I'm not saying that I'm going to forgive her or her team.
I'm your leader, so her blood should be on my hands.
Sorry, but that's not your decision to make.
Then you're gonna punish them, right?
They sided with a vampire on the battlefield, which led to our troops being ambushed.
Like I said, you don't get to decide what happens to them.
Fine, then.
Prove you've got what it takes to lead us and punish them!
This entire mission has turned into a giant shitstorm.
Just look at us!
We've lost several of our comrades and our commander.
But we kept moving forward, following orders!
And look how well that's working out.
You want us to forgive these traitors and stand by?
Are we supposed to just lie down and die out here?
Escape in the chopper.
Then lead the vampires to a trap waiting for them in Shinjuku.
That's what our final mission was.
Only thing is, Gurren's not the one who planned this.
Then who did?
Lieutenant General Kuruto Hiragi.
Of course, I'm sick of the Hiragis.
The selfish orders they give out only serve to give them more power.
Well, I refuse to follow it anymore!
Just calm down.
Freaking out isn't going to help us figure out what...
Don't you dare tell me to calm down!
We're abandoning this mission.
I'm going back to rescue the lieutenant colonel.
If he's going back, so am I.
You coming?
If this wasn't Gurren's mission, I don't see any reason to finish it, right?
Goshi, Mito, Shinya, goodbye.
Shigure!
Sayuri!
Think about this!
This is starting to get ugly.
What should we do?
Hold on, Narumi.
I know I'm disobeying orders.
Go ahead and court-martial me for all I care.
Ah, just shut up for a second and listen to me.
I'm trying to tell you that we're aborting this mission together.
What?
Let's do it.
We'll ignore the orders from High Command.
From now on, the Demon Company has one goal.
The rescue of Lieutenant Colonel Gurren Ichinose.
Seriously?
You heard him. Let's go.
We're not going to abandon our friend when he needs our help.
It looks like we missed an impressive battle here.
Start talking, maggot.
What were your plans?
You'll have to hit me harder than that.
Queen Cruel specifically ordered us not to kill him.
Soon he'll be begging to be put out of his misery.
All right.
This is starting to get a little painful.
Time to leak some false intel and buy myself a break.
Let's see.
I've got to get these bastards to Shinjuku somehow.
They've probably beat me enough to believe I've broken.
It's not nap time for the livestock yet.
What a pleasure to see you, Crowley.
It's been too long.
Five nobles were killed today.
The humans knew their locations.
I'm positive that you had something to do with this, Lord Farad.
I'm hurt.
There's nothing worse than selling out your friends, right?
That's despicable.
Yeah.
True.
But that's not what concerns me.
What bothers me is that you gave the humans my location, too.
And here I was under the impression that I was your friend.
But surely you enjoyed the fight.
Well, yeah, I guess it was a pretty good time.
Then you should be thanking me instead.
Besides, everyone knows that we're friends, Crowley.
No one will suspect I leaked info if you were attacked.
I see.
So you were the one behind this.
You're only half right.
There's actually another puppeteer pulling the strings along with me.
Oh?
Who is it?
Him.
You must have some kind of death wish, human.
How dare you!
Okay, I've had enough of this.
It's Shinjuku.
You're dead, filthy human!
Okay, stop it.
He's saying something.
I don't care!
The lieutenant colonel is a half-demon.
Hmm?
A half-demon?
Although he's actually close to becoming complete.
Every day he struggles to keep two personalities under control inside his body.
One is an idealist who wants nothing more than to protect his troops and his friends from harm.
Come on now.
You've had more than enough of this, my darling.
Relax and let me take over a while.
Get lost.
My poor little soldier.
You don't even have the strength to push me away right now.
But the other personality isn't so nice.
It's his dead ex-girlfriend.
A perfectionist who's been turned into a demon.
Look, the monster is coming out.
You're dead, human!
Die!
Enjoy your last few seconds alive, bloodsucker.
What?
How dare you speak to me like that?
Give it here, my hero.
Oh, I see.
You're the one in control.
Help her!
Kill him!
Stay where you are!
Now then, you're Mahiru Hiragi's messenger.
So where is she?
Mahiru is dead.
My deal was with her before the world ended.
If she's dead, then there's no reason for me to keep you alive.
Our agreement is null and void in this circumstance.
Then go ahead and kill me.
Oh, that's right.
You can't do it.
You've already betrayed your kind and need the humans to bail your sorry ass out, right?
The serif of the end?
The experiment has to succeed today or you're totally screwed.
Smart thinking.
Make them believe you're still on their side, not a complete traitor.
They'll be testing it at the airport.
Attention, men!
The humans are reassembling at the Nagaya Airport.
Old units, move out!
Ma'am!
So, what's going to happen now, Ferret?
What's the endgame?
The transformation of the world.
Vampires?
Yuichi!
Right.
Don't fire!
They're...
They're ours.
Those are Demon Army aircraft.
Big sister!
Serpent,ansa...
...
Hey!
He's the one who tortured us.
Good нуж aim.
Kurato.
Shiragi.
Attention! I'm Lieutenant General Kureto Hiragi.
As you likely know, my family controls the Demon Army.
I've heard stories about him.
Me too.
Rumor has it he's next in line as head of the Hiragis and the army.
Because of your efforts, we're looking at total victory over the Vampires.
The sacrifices of the Moon Demon Company will not have been in vain.
You have ensured humanity's survival.
My team will take over from here.
Enjoy some much-deserved downtime.
Disarm and relax.
Does that mean our mission's over?
Sounds like it.
Makoto, did you hear that?
Everyone, stay at attention and ready to fight just in case.
Total victory, huh?
Vampire nobles are headed this way as we speak.
So how do you plan to defeat them, brother?
Brutally.
We lost a lot of comrades here.
Don't we deserve to know what your plan is?
Where is Gurren?
He was captured by the Vampires.
Huh?
Please tell me you're joking.
Damn it.
That fool.
Is he turning on me as well?
Which personality was in control when they took him?
Huh?
Come on.
You haven't figured it out yet.
Figured what out?
Well, he did always try to keep his comrades protected and in the dark.
But I'm surprised you didn't catch on since you were so close.
What are you talking about?
Gurren's been taken!
That's enough.
Your part in this is over.
Aoi.
Do it.
Yes, sir.
Wait, Kurito.
What in the hell is going on?
I told you, your role in this is complete.
What are you planning to do?
Hey!
Stand down, right now.
I don't know who you are, but I told you to relax.
Follow my orders.
Screw your orders!
What?
You think you can show up here and...
Calm down.
Makoto, ease up.
Not good.
What have you done, brother?
Don't bother.
You can't hope to protect him.
We completed an impossible suicide mission behind enemy lines.
We did what you asked of us, so just let us go.
And overlook this soldier's rebellious attitude?
Alright.
I'll let it slide.
Don't want to spoil the fun.
Besides, he's going to die soon anyway.
Shit.
Begin!
Get push him!
Arison Kin.
Arise.
No.
Akoto.
Run!
Arison Kin.
Right.
Arison Kin!
Arison Kin.
Damn you!
I'll kill you murdering bastard!
Back off!
Don't you see I've given these soldiers honorable deaths?
Their sacrifice is for humanity's future.
I spared them!
Just shut up!
You saved me!
Stop hurting my friend!
We need to retreat!
Don't worry, Shinoa.
You're safe.
Even if you don't act like it, you're still technically a Hiragi.
Run.
Die then.
Who's back?
Nice save.
But he...
You're here.
Of course.
You okay?
Yeah, that was kinda close.
I told you.
We shouldn't have come.
This is a huge mess.
Humans attacking other humans.
Just look.
No.
I'm glad we came.
Bastard.
What are you doing to my comrades?
That's one of Gurren's black demon kids.
Do it.
you. We shouldn't have come. This is a huge mess. Humans attacking other humans. Just
look. No. I'm glad we came. Bastard. What are you doing to my comrades? That's one of
Gurren's black demon kids. Do it. They're coming from the container. Yuichi!
Damn it. What have they got hidden inside that thing? It doesn't matter. Stop it.
Let's get out of here. Come on, you.
All units, move in. I don't want a single human to survive.
This is the end. We're destroying the vampires right here. Do it for humanity!
Holy crap. What should we do? Don't panic. This is a great opportunity.
Yeah. They're not paying attention to us anymore. This is our chance to escape.
You kids go ahead and run while you can. The seasoned pros will provide you with plenty
of cover. You guys.
I'll clear a path for us. Let's go!
What are you doing? That's it. No more of my friends are going to die today. You idiot. You're too far out.
No more!
Gurren, you're alright. Let's go!
Good. You're here. I was hoping that you would be.
We'll be right back.
Next time on Seraph of the End, Seraph of the End.